[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
I'm throwing you, okay?
Hey, Jung Woo Jae.
I did it, right?
Right?
Oh my Gosh!
What is this?
Hey, Jung Woo Jae.
Get up.
Hurry, get up.
Yoon Ha Na?
Let's do it one more time.
Why did they call Dangun Wanggeom of Gojoseon the king of theocracy?
Hey, what's with the attitude?
He didn't only have a hand in politics,
- but took part in rituals... - When we go back,
we get Woo Jae back into sports.
What will you do?
I'll be the one in your body, not you.
Don't worry about it.
Yoon Ha Ru's body?
It's already been perfected by senior year.
- In the roots of our history... - I wonder if Yoon Ha Na is doing okay?
there were communicators of the unseen world...
Yoon Ha Ru!
Faster!
Come on!
It's too heavy!
We'll start over if I catch you!
Come on!
Faster, faster!
Perfected? What a liar!
I don't like this at all.
That's not how you do it.
You need to use sudden force!
Sudden, get it?
Yoon Ha Ru.
Flip your opponent over like this.
Sudden force, see.
This is how you do it.
Give it some more oomph.
Were you starved as a kid? Why are you so weak?
The sun's going to set at this rate!
Hurry, let's wrap this up.
Get up, come on!
- Let's go. - We're almost there, come on!
Let's go!
Thanks.
- They believed in the power of nature - Jung Woo Jae...
- and prayed for communal prosperity - starts judo again...
- via rituals. - made it into the national team...
That is why the leader of that era...
- Okay, that's done. - was not only a king of the people...
but a bridge between the gods and humans.
Like a shaman.
Can I really trust Yoon Ha Na?
- I hope she doesn't screw up. - When the soul leaves the body,
they believed the body to be an empty husk.
So, if the husk got taken over by a stray soul...
or got lost,
what did they do?
[Shaman] Back then, to them, shamans and rituals...
were like the doctors of the present times.
It was healing.
They believed shamans to be pathfinders for spirits.
A spiritual guide, so to speak.
Sir!
What is it, Yoon Ha Na?
It's rare that you have a question.
That "spiritual guide" stuff...
Do you think it could still fly in our present day?
Well, historically speaking...
the form may have changed,
but the idea of spirituality still exists, yes.
It's a cultural tradition, you see.
Why?
Do you want to know the future? Thinking of going to a fortune teller?
No, nothing like that.
Well, just the fact that Yoon Ha Na is awake during class...
- is enough to make me happy. - A spiritual guide...
Now, another point to be mindful of...
- Not bad. - Can anyone tell me what it is?
The seasonal rituals of the Three Hans.
- A spiritual... - Every December,
- guide... - there was a ritual called Yeonggo.
Which nation was that?
All done.
It'll get better soon, I guess.
Can't you knock?
Who cares if I saw?
It's my body, anyway.
It's just a sore muscle, no need for all that.
What a weakling.
What do you want?
Yeah, we need to have an emergency meeting.
Are you certain?
Of what?
The trials. Are you?
I'm doing my best.
That's not enough.
My body may be a gift from the skies above,
but you lack the software to make use of the top-tier hardware.
Top-tier? You've got to be kidding me.
Well? Any good ideas?
Personal training. Starting today.
Personal training?
Check back into the dorms starting tomorrow.
Good job, and good luck.
See, judo is all about aura.
Once you get a grip, you use your "you're dead meat" stare.
Like so.
Hey, it's late now.
You'll wake up all our neighbors.
The ferocity of a judo player knows no rest, day or night! It's on 24/7!
Yeah, yeah, sure.
Where are your eyes? I said look here!
You need to win the staring contest first, okay?
See the fire in my eyes, huh?
Beat me, come on!
I don't know about the fire...
but I see your eye boogers.
Ugh, seriously!
My fierceness, resilience and my toughness...
are nowhere to be found.
Is this truly the end of my life as a judo player?
Why is he texting me instead of just coming in?
- Woo Jae? - Yeah.
Huh?
Why is he asking me to go see a movie?
A movie?
Ha Na, do you have time tomorrow?
Do you want to go see a movie with me?
So, what's happening right now is...
he's not asking me...
but you, right?
Well, I think so.
Okay! Can Yoon Ha Ru come, too?
By the way, why not come inside?
Why is he getting in the way?
This is not going well.
Wait, no.
This is my chance to make things clear.
Alright, the three of us it is, then.
I'm heading in now.
[Banana milk]
It's Yoon Ha Na.
The one I really like is...
Yoon Ha Na.
Yoon Ha Na, Yoon Ha Na...
What's taking Ha Ru so long?
What a pain in my foot.
Let's go.
You... can't be serious about going out like this.
I am.
What's wrong?
Get inside.
Where?
Your room, come on! Hurry!
- Go inside. - What, why?
- Inside, now. - Why?
Stand up straight.
You want me to wear this?
Shut it.
This seems to fit nicely.
I'm not wearing a dress!
Hey!
Stay still.
Come here.
Ugh, you...
I said, come here.
- All done. - It's over, right?
Sit down.
Why?
I said, sit!
You're not leaving like that.
Over here.
Damn it.
What is wrong with him?
Where's Jung Woo Jae?
He's right outside.
Do you have to walk like that?
Just be normal for once. Please?
I'm begging you.
No, hear this.
Something's off.
Off?
I'm constantly feeling this gentle breeze down there.
It's like something's missing.
It's unsettling.
Can you please keep your legs together?
I should sue you for defamation!
Ugh, alright, alright.
Oh, Jung Woo Jae!
What took you so long?
I was at the convenience store.
Let's go inside, Woo Jae.
Uh, okay.
Ha Na.
Have this.
Milk? At the movies?
Is this why you were late?
Yeah, I noticed that you drink this a lot.
Coke is the best for watching movies.
We're not kids, who's drinking milk?
I guess so...
I'll drink it.
That banana milk...
I want it.
Give it to me.
Okay.
That's so funny.
So hilarious.
Thanks.
Private Yoon Ha Ru, reporting for duty!
What is wrong with you? Sit down!
Sorry.
God, I hate him so much!
♪ I'll wait through countless mishaps ♪
♪ I'll smile through all the pain ♪
♪ Don't leave, don't give up yet ♪
♪ See this love grow deeper the more you push me away ♪
♪ You can hold my tongue, but the world will still know ♪
♪ So why are you the only one clueless? ♪
♪ Why don't you see the man who will keep you safe? ♪
- I ate that up! - Practice harder and try for a perfect score!
♪ You ♪
♪ When I fall down ♪
♪ Don't waver, help me up time and time again ♪
♪ With your strong gaze ♪
♪ And you ♪
♪ When I'm having a hard time ♪
♪ You came for me to the edge of the cliff ♪
♪ Without fail ♪
♪ And held my two hands in yours ♪
♪ Though I have nothing to offer ♪
♪ Nothing to show ♪
♪ But today, for you ♪
♪ I sing this song ♪
♪ Tonight ♪
♪ In your two eyes ♪
Take a break, Ha Na.
Like you did?
Like when you gave up judo?
But what do you get after running away?
You ended up a bodyguard.
Don't be scared.
Just be yourself.
To me, no one shines brighter...
than you, Yoon Ha Na.
Thank goodness...
Woo Jae!
No, wait!
What do I do?
♪ Never say goodbye ♪
♪ Because this world, to me ♪
♪ is only you and I ♪
Oh, my throat hurts. I'm going to the convenience store.
Are you guys going?
I'm good.
We'll wait for you.
Hey. Why the long face?
No reason.
Just thinking about someone.
Who?
Just someone.
Not the sharpest tool in the shed.
Well, who is it?
Hey, Yoon Ha Ru.
What are you guys doing?
It was buy two, get one. Big bro is buying! Want one?
Oh, I'm good.
Want it?
I must be out of my mind.
What is wrong with me?
Get it together, Jung Woo Jae.
The person I like is...
Yoon Ha Na.
You know...
Yeah?
I... actually, I...
Yeah, what is it? Spit it out.
I like you!
Huh?
What?
I...
I like you.
Jung Woo Jae, you idiot...
How is that a proper confession?
In what world was that a good idea?
Why did I do that in front of a convenience store?
Yoon Ha Na.
I... actually, I...
I like you!
Huh?
What?
Why did it have to be then?
Why right then?
Why?
Oh, man, what do I do?
Wow, he just confessed to me!
He did it to me, not you.
Well, it's me now!
Think about it, what if he tried to, like,
kiss me, or something?
Oh, I'm about to throw up.
God, can you stay still for a minute?
You saw it too, didn't you?
You saw the way he looked at me, right?
It was so intense, I thought I'd melt!
It's not just my problem, though. How would you feel?
Imagine him and me holding hands...
and hugging...
- and kissing... - Stop!
Oh, seriously.
Shamans and rituals were like the doctors of the present times.
It was healing.
They believed shamans to be pathfinders for spirits.
A spiritual guide, so to speak.
Hey, let's switch.
- What? - Our bodies.
So, go back to the future?
We can't, not yet.
We need to see Woo Jae make the national team.
No, right now.
Let's swap right here, right now.
- Huh? - Well, we haven't tried anything.
That's because that doesn't make sense!
Well, does this right now make sense to you?
We've already been swapped, there's no logic to this!
It makes no sense!
- Well, yeah, I guess so. - Let's try it.
I'm desperate, please!
Are you seriously worried that he might kiss you?
It's about judo.
Huh?
The trials!
There's not much time left.
He's obviously going to make it in.
But, well...
I need to at least come in 2nd place.
Yoon Ha Ru...
You were really worried.
I shouldn't be pressuring you as your big brother.
Sorry about that.
No.
Let's try.
The sooner, the better.
Okay.
So...
How are we doing this?
Shamanism.
Shamanism?
Sis!
You're standing on the edge of a cliff, sis.
One more step and it all crumbles.
That tower that you worked so hard on building.
Pardon?
There's no use pretending.
Your insides are all burnt black.
It's just ashes in there.
How did you know?
And with you, mister...
Who are you?
Who are you, you fox!
Some wretch has taken over your body.
Who? Who is it?
Oh my, Grandmama...
You like it there, don't you!
He's young,
and handsome...
he's a great source of energy.
There's no place better, huh?
You love it, don't you!
Grandmama likes it in you.
She looks like she wants to stay.
So, an old lady? Who is she?
Sis, your troubles are also because this hag is in your twin brother.
You're twins, so it takes double the effort.
Double...
the effort.
Well, how much will it cost?
10 million won!
It's a rip-off.
10 million?
Yes.
Should we ask Mom?
Hey.
Hey!
Kiddo.
Is it you?
The one who's selling my name to rip people off?
You... you're lying.
Open your eyes.
Grandma?
Are... are you actually there?
How low can you go, ripping money off of kids?
Kiddo.
If you keep using that money to satiate your own greed,
your guardian spirit will get mad and leave you for good.
No use crying about it to me when it happens.
No... no way.
It's not really her.
Which hag are you! Who are you!
Stop it with the hag!
Hey...
Yeah.
My grandma says...
if you keep calling her a hag,
I should rip your tongue out and throw it at the tapestry over there.
Do you want to see her angry?
Get those hands off the table!
I will, I am, I have!
I won't, I'm sorry, please! Just leave!
Please, leave!
Leave!
"Spiritual guide," my foot.
We're broke high schoolers! 10 million?
And out of mom's pockets, no less?
Your brain must've gone back in time as well.
Have you lost it?
Isn't it the effort that counts?
If you hit me now,
you're just a dude hitting a girl!
- Wait up! - Screw off.
Why?
I said, bugger off!
Wait for me!
Yoon Ha Na.
What?
That wasn't very big-brotherly of me to put you under pressure.
Sorry.
Whatever.
I wasn't thinking hard enough.
And now I realize
that I need to think even less.
- What? - See.
Let's think simply.
The very reason we're here...
is Jung Woo Jae.
Not my trials.
So?
Saving Woo Jae comes first.
Let's see him make it into the team,
and return to the present.
What about you?
What about it?
I've been a judo player my whole life.
Missing my shot at this one trial won't spell out the end for me.
Oh, come on, it's fine.
Go on, go!
I'll... do my best.
Yoon Ha Ru, your life...
I'll protect it as well.
- But... - What now?
Jung Woo Jae.
What do we do with him?
Huh?
It's fine.
It's not fine.
It's fine...
I like you!
Huh? What?
It's not fine.
Not at all.
This is driving me nuts!
Come on!
Alright, I'm going.
Don't mess around, okay?
I got it, stop treating me like an idiot!
- Go on! - I said alright!
Yoon Ha Ru!
Go, go!
Ha Na.
Hi.
- I... - I...
You go first.
Okay.
Well...
About... what you said last night.
Oh, that.
I must've freaked you out.
Yeah, for real, it freaked me...
Well, it was a bit surprising, I guess.
But...
Well, what I meant to say is...
I...
Thank you.
Huh?
For feeling that way towards me.
Thanks.
It's nothing, really.
The thing is, though...
I, uh...
Right now,
you're about to face a very important trial.
I need to study for my college entrance, too.
Yeah.
Which is why I think...
I get what you mean.
Huh?
No, wait.
- I'm not finished... - You're right, Ha Na.
I was being too rash.
I wanted to wait until after the trials to properly confess to you.
That day was a mistake.
Hey, no.
Don't call it a mistake.
I'll confess to you again, properly...
after the trials.
When I make the national team,
and you get admitted to your dream college...
we'll talk again.
Oh, yeah.
Okay, let's do that.
Yeah, I like the sound of that.
Thank you for starting this conversation with me.
Oh, it's nothing.
No need to thank me.
That's a relief.
It's settled, then.
Now...
let's just focus on him making it into the team.
[National team trials, D-15]
[National team trials, D-12]
[National team trials, D-5]
[National team trials, D-day] This day calls for a barbecue!
Not pork, no, it has to be beef.
Today's the day.
Yeah.
Let's give it our best.
Yeah, let's do this.
- Everyone on board? - Yes, sir!
Today's dinner...
It's up to you whether I pay for a chicken dinner or a beef banquet!
Prove yourselves on the mat, got it?
- Yes, sir! - Okay!
You heard him, folks!
We'll run him bankrupt with a beef banquet!
We'll show him what we're made of!
- Let's do this! - Let's go!
- Beef! Beef! - Beef! Beef!
Mom! We need to leave!
Your mom always takes so long to get ready to go anywhere ever!
Takes a lifetime.
Mom! Do you even know what time it is? What if there's traffic?
We won't be late.
Stop fussing!
The trials will last the whole darn day anyway.
Well, Ha Ru will only be competing for so long.
Come on, come on!
- Alright, let's go! - Let's!
- We're leaving now! - Let's go!
- You've got everything, right? - Yeah!
- Okay, let's go! - Go!
Oh, wait, wait!
What is it now?
I forgot something! Wait!
You're for sure your mother's daughter!
Hush and go get the car ready!
Woo Jae, this is the day.
After today,
things will be different.
I'll end our days of pain and anguish.
I will make sure of it.
You think Ha Ru will do well?
Of course.
But honey, have you noticed?
The tension today is way stronger.
Yes, but I don't see why.
This isn't the first time Ha Ru has competed.
Don't you worry, Madam Jung Yeong Sook.
Don't forget to bring this tomorrow.
Yeah.
We'll be able to make it back tomorrow, right?
We will.
Woo Jae will make it in, no matter what.
And me, as well...
No,
I mean, you...
will make it, too.
I'll try my absolute best.
Don't exert yourself.
Just don't get hurt.
Okay.
Ha Ru takes after me, he'll do fine.
Please make it in, Ha Ru...
Oh, please, please...
Are you even listening to me?
[Shinil Sports Complex]
Let's do this!
Look at the thug.
He's gotten even more buff!
That's scary.
- You scared? - Yeah...
That's cute.
He's going to cry today.
Hey, look at him.
Well, well.
Look who it is.
I thought you quit judo. Crawling back like a dog?
Have you no shame?
Why's that?
Did you realize once you left the judo scene
that you're no good for anything else?
See you later.
What's his problem?
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Who the hell is he?
Baekyeon High School's judo thug?
A chick?
That's Lee Hyeong Won.
Lee Hyeong Won?
Let's go.
Okay.
Everyone!
You are all nameless on the mat.
Either you are a winner or a loser.
You'll climb off that mat with either of those names.
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
I'll make it short. Just remember three things.
Don't let go of the collar, keep eye contact,
and... endure. Whatever it takes.
Understood?
- Yes, sir! - Yes, sir!
Today...
we'll have that beef banquet!
Good luck.
There he is!
Go, Yoon Ha Ru!
- Show them! - Go, Yoon Ha Ru!
Start!
[National team trials, round of 16] [Lee Hyeong Won : Pyo Gyeong Woo]
Yes, that's it! Tear him apart!
[Lee Hyeong Won]
The judo thug, Lee Hyeong Won!
He was talented, but he dropped off the face of the earth one day.
I wonder what he's doing now.
[Jung Woo Jae : Kim Dong Gil]
Go!
Start!
Good!
That's it, Jung Woo Jae!
[Yoon Ha Ru : Jang Won]
Start!
Yes, defend! Defense position, there you go!
Stop!
- It's okay! - Thank goodness!
Go, Ha Ru!
Yoon Ha Ru!
Don't give up!
Don't give up yet!
Don't you dare give up!
Let's go!
Start!
- Go, go, Yoon Ha Ru! - Go!
Go, go!
You're doing great!
- Full point! - Let's go!
Stop!
- Yoon Ha Ru! - Yoon Ha Ru!
[National team trials, round of 8] [Jung Woo Jae : Park Sung Soo]
Pinning!
Half point!
Full point!
[Round of 8] [Yoon Ha Ru : Lee Hyeong Won]
You dare hit Woo Jae's shoulder?
You bastard...
You're dead.
Start!
I can do this!
Yoon Ha Ru won all of these matches anyway.
I can protect everyone...
Are you okay?
Go, go!
Yoon Ha Na.
You can do it!
Start!
Wait, that's...
Full point!
That's it, Yoon Ha Na.
See it through, Ha Na.
Please...
No, Yoon Ha Na...
Do it for Ha Ru!
Don't!
Come on!
What's going on?
It'll be okay.
- Go! Check on him! - Oh, wait...
You'll have to go see a doctor.
Get some tests done.
Oh, no, my baby...
It'll be alright.
It's no big deal.
[Round of 4] [Jung Woo Jae : Lee Hyeong Won]
Start!
Oh, right.
Woo Jae's semifinal will start soon...
Oh, I'll go keep watch.
- Another ice pack, please. - Alright.
- Beef banquet! - Beef, beef, beef!
What?
Lee Hyeong Won...
This is how he disappeared?
Hey, Lee Hyeong Won!
Where are you going?
- What's it to you? - I asked you a question.
Get lost.
Why?
Are you giving up because of one lost match?
Shut it.
I'll still punch a girl.
It's not over for you yet.
There's a repechage, you know.
You can secure a bronze medal if you're lucky.
A bronze?
What good is that?
Who's going to acknowledge me for a 3rd place?
Are you that out of touch?
What's wrong with coming in 3rd place?
It's better than running away without even trying.
Way cooler than the pathetic rat you're acting like right now.
It's not even worth the comparison, really.
What did you just say?
Hey, hey! The repechage, it's...
- Uh, I... - No way.
We need to go see a doctor.
Let's go.
No, but...
- But I... - Ha Ru.
Let's go to the hospital.
Get back in there.
You still have a chance at this.
Choose.
Do you want to be a judo player,
or end up a miserable twat?
[Baekyeon High School]
I'm sorry.
You told me not to get injured,
but I couldn't even manage that.
What are you on about?
Don't tell me...
You're conscious of me? That's so not you.
I wanted to...
protect your life as well, you know.
Are you crying?
How did you manage to memorize all those lines as an actress with your empty noggin?
- What? - We came here for one reason.
Don't tell me you forgot it already.
Jung Woo Jae.
Not my trials. Jung Woo Jae, got it?
Idiot.
We saw him make it into the team.
Our work is over here.
I'll save my own skin. Don't make a big deal out of it.
Well, now, let's go back!
- But... - What now?
We don't know how to.
Not yet.
Damn, you're right.
That didn't work.
I guess just dropping it isn't what triggers it.
Well, let's try whatever we can.
If it wants a fight, we'll give it a fight.
Huh? What's up with the weather?
Hey, are you alright?
I'm fine.
Huh?
What the...
My alumna, Shin Bi Gyeong?
Hello, it's 2013.
This is the after-party for Yongwon University's Department of Film!
Coming to you live!
- Applaud! - 2013?
Did the rain trigger another time leap?
Our alumni are getting blackout drunk right now, as we speak!
Let's see for ourselves.
- Chug, chug, chug! - Ye Rang!
- Film is life! - Right, around this time, I assumed
- she'd become an actress. - And life is a long take!
- And Jun Mo... He looks so young looking back. - Chug it, chug!
Han Soo Hyuk is... well, Han Soo Hyuk.
Let's hand it over to reporter Yoon Ha Na.
Here you go, reporter Yoon Ha Na...
Did you just call me Yoon Ha Na?
Huh? It's me!
It's Yoon Ha Na!
But why 2013?
Why not 2026? Why is it 2013?
What's wrong, Ha Na?
You alright, Ha Na?
I'd be 21 in 2013...
So, if he's 21...
Woo Jae must be serving in the army.
- Hey, where are you going? - Yoon Ha Na!
Where are you going?
Why is this happening?
What went wrong?
[Beast] Why won't he answer?
Oh, my purse!
Thief!
- Move! - It's a thief! A thief!
Move!
- He's a thief! - Out of the way!
You're not going anywhere!
Piss off!
Let go!
Are you alright?
Woo Jae!
Are you hurt?
You scum!
Stay down!
Oh, thank you.
Ha Na.
You sure you're okay?
Oh, yeah, I'm totally fine.
Are you sure you're okay?
Of course I'm fine.
I got your purse back, didn't I?
No, I mean, you...
Where do you live now?
What about judo?
Are you that drunk, Ha Na?
I...
I quit, remember?
- Judo... - What? Why?
But you were first place in the national trial! Why would you quit judo?
I mean, why did you?
Everyone's drinking a lot.
I guess it's fair, being the after-party of our campus festival.
Our department seemed like they wouldn't stop drinking, too.
So I left after I got some dinner in me.
- Your department? - Yeah.
By the way, we have a whopping three new female students.
Becoming a bodyguard was their childhood dream.
How cool is that?
Bodyguard?
Yeah.
[Beast]
Just a moment.
Okay.
What took you so long?
[Yoon's Raw Fish Restaurant] Yoon Ha Ru, where are you right now?
- Yoon Ha Na. - Yeah?
Where the hell are you?
Haesol.
Haesol?
What are you doing there?
Working part-time at our parents' restaurant.
I'm not a judo player.
I gave up... on judo.
What?
Nothing's going as we expected.
Everyone was worried about the two idiots who knew nothing other than judo.
How do I even do this?
Chef.
Why choose to be a bodyguard?
I have someone I want to protect.
[That Summer, Us: Male Actor Audition] What if...
that someone became the protector?
[We will protect Jung Woo Jae!] Ta-da!
Woo Jae...
I'm going to make him an actor.
Physically adept, action-ready, and a killer gaze. That's you!
- Me? - You'll be Jung Woo Jae, worldwide star!
Turns out, it wasn't just the medal that I wanted to take from you.
If you can't put faith in yourself,
put faith in me, who believes in you.